https://www.littleswitz.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyReturn Policy:
Please note: Season Passes are non-refundable, non-transferable, and may not be resold. If you cannot use your pass due to lack of snow, medical reasons, pregnancy, divorce, moving away or any other reason, you will not receive a refund. However, if you protect your investment with Season Pass Insurance and you are not able to use your pass for medical reasons, we'll give you a pro-rated credit for the following season.
Privacy Policy:
This statement sets out how Little Switzerland, LLC will treat your personal information.
Little Switzerland, LLC may collect, store and use: information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website; information that you send to Little Switzerland, LLCusing the website request form; and any other information that you choose to send to Little Switzerland, LLC
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy statement or in relevant parts of the website. Little Switzerland, LLC may use your personal information to administer the website and deal with your requests relating to the website.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy statement, Little Switzerland, LLC may disclose information about you: (a) to the extent that Little Switzerland, LLC . is required to do so by law; (b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; (c) in order to establish, exercise or defend Little Switzerland, LLC legal rights; (d) to any ofLittle Switzerland, LLC agents, suppliers or subcontractors (but only as reasonably necessary for our purposes as set out above); and (e) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which Little Switzerland, LLC is (or is contemplating) selling.
Little Switzerland,LLC will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Little Switzerland, LLC will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and Little Switzerland, LLC cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
Little Switzerland, LLC may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on theLittle Switzerland, LLC website.
You may instruct Little Switzerland, LLC to provide you with any personal information Little Switzerland, LLC holds about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee. You may instruct Little Switzerland, LLC not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time.
Little Switzerland, LLC uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to the website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html. A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the webserver to identify and track the web browser. Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.
